https://www.interform400.com/en/privacy-policy

Newsletter Sign Up
For customers
Report a problem
Go to InterForm Support Center to submit a new ticket for our support team.
Submit a ticket
Contact Us
ProductsServicesInterForm ServicesBeing InterForm customerPartnersBecome a partnerFind partnerTechnology partnersWhy InterFormCase studiesERP's best friendInspiration Why Output ManagementSeparate your Output from your ERPThe right tool for the jobSupportDevelopmentDocumentationFAQSupportVideosCompanyAbout usContact usNewsROIAutomotiveERP
Native IBM i product line
InterForm400AdvancedPDF400InterArchive400InterExcel400InterFax400InterPJL400InterRFID400InterSigning400InterWord400InterXML400SpoolToXML400WinPrint400
Platform Independent
InterFormNGAdvancedPDFInterRFIDTxtToXML
Try Software
InterForm
Product: Privacy Policy
InterForm NG
Product: Privacy Policy
Privacy & Cookie Policy
InterForm A/S (“InterForm”), has created this privacy and cookie policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy and confidentiality of our online activities (website, newsletter, surveys, support ticket, etc.) for our visitors/users. We endeavour to comply with any data protection legislation in the countries in which we operate. The following discloses how InterForm processes your personal data and how we handle cookie.
Who is responsible for your personal data?
InterForm is the data controller of your personal data. InterForm controls the ways your personal data is collected and the purposes for which your personal data is used.
What types of personal data do we collect?
We collect the following types of personal data:
Name
Email address
Company name
Phone number
IP address
Location
Time stamps
Language preference
Activity tracking
InterForm will never ask for or collect any sensitive personal data like your ethnic origin, health, religious beliefs etc. In addition, we will under no circumstances ask for personal identifiers, such as, account numbers, PINs, passwords, voice scans and credit card numbers, etc.
When do we collect personal data?
Personal data may be collected when you use the following functions:
On an opt-in (voluntary) basis for making contact by email, phone and address and for making use of website features like downloads or event registration.
When you subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, open a support ticket, download a product or documentation, register as a customer, etc.
Furthermore, we collect behavioural data e.g. if you click a link in our email campaigns.
What personal data is used for and on which legal basis?
We may use the personal data we collect from you to:
Personalize your web experience on our website
To provide you with our products and services
To handle your customer service requests
To improve our products and services
To send you newsletters about new products, special offers, other information which we think may be of your interest or for market research purposes
To provide you with marketing material
Ensure our legal compliance
Statistics and analyses
We process your personal data on one of the following legal bases:
Your consent
When the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract or in order to take steps at the request of you prior to entering a contract
To comply with our legal obligations
To pursue our legitimate interests
The legitimate interest of InterForm is to perform statistics and analyses and to improve our products and services.
How long is your personal data stored?
When you use our website we sometimes collect and process your personal data based on your consent.
Consent
When you use our website we sometimes collect and process your personal data based on your consent.
Please note that you may withdraw your consent at any time. Please contact us, if you wish to withdraw your consent.
You can withdraw your consent by unsubscribing in the bottom of our newsletter/emails.
If you withdraw your consent, we will stop the processing of your personal data, unless we are entitled or obliged to continue the processing or storage of your personal data on another legal basis, e.g. pursuant to legislation.
Withdrawal of your consent will not affect the lawfulness of the processing prior to the withdrawal.
If you withdraw your consent in whole or partly you may not be able to use the functions offered on our website in full.
Your rights
You have a right of access to the personal data, which we process and store about you, subject to certain statutory exceptions.
Furthermore, you have the right to object to the collection and further processing of your personal data. Moreover, you have the right to rectification of your personal data, or to require us to restrict the processing of your personal data.
If you so request, we will erase the personal data which we have registered on you without undue delay, unless we may continue the processing on another legal basis, e.g. if the processing is necessary to defend a legal claim or to comply with a request from you.
Under certain circumstances, you may also request that we provide you with an overview of your personal data that you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and request us to transmit such data to another data controller.
If you wish to exercise your rights as described above, please contact us (see contact information below).
In connection with requests regarding your rights, we kindly ask you to provide us with sufficient information in order for us to handle your request, including name and email address, and to identify you. If necessary, we may ask for further information. We will reply to your request as soon as possible and no later than one month.
If you disagree with how we process your personal data or the purposes for which we process your personal data, you may either contact us, take legal actions at the ordinary courts or you may lodge a complaint with:
Danish Data Protection AgencyBorgergade 28, 5.DK 1300 Copenhagen KThis email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.+45 33 19 32 00
Personal data received from third parties
We may also receive your personal data from our business partners who provide services to you on our behalf e.g. when you buy products or provide feedback on our services.
InterForm is not responsible for how our business partners/resellers collect or store personal data. Any sensitive personal data or personal data obtained by partners without consent is not used or saved by InterForm.
Security
We have implemented appropriate technical and organisational security measures to ensure an adequate security level and require that trusted third parties who process your personal datan do the same. Accordingly, we use our best efforts to ensure the confidentiality and integrity of your personal data.
Links
This website contains links to our partners which we believe is helpful for our visitors. InterForm is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. If you visit a website of a third party, you should read the privacy policy and other relevant policies of the owner of the website.
Cookies
We use both persistent and session cookies. Persistent cookies like standard Google Analytics as well as cookies for saving your language preferences. These sessions will expire after one year.
Session cookies are short term cookies that improve your user experience. These cookies expire with the current session, do not contain any personal data, and are not shared with any other website. Should you not want any cookies from our website, we recommend you adjust your browser settings to provide the desired blocking.
How do you delete or disable cookies?
The procedure for deleting or disabling cookies on your device depends on the browser you are using.
If you are using a PC, you may delete cookies by using the keyboard shortcut [CTRL]+[SHIFT]+[Delete]
If this procedure is not successful or if you are using a Mac computer, please follow the guidelines via the following links depending on the browser you are using:
Microsoft Edge
Mozilla Firefox
Google Chrome
Safari
Opera
Flash cookies
- iPad, iPhone, iPod touch
- Android
Third-party disclosure
InterForm does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal data. InterForm does not share personal data with third parties except with the consent of you, and always in accordance with this policy.
You can find a list of third parties who receive your personal data here:
Google Analytics: https://www.google.com/analytics/
The Rocket Science Group LLC d/b/a MailChimp: https://mailchimp.com/
Should you wish not to provide data to Google Analytics you can prevent this be installing a Browser Add-on: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
We will transfer your personal data to third parties outside EU/EEA, however, we warrant that such third parties have provided appropriate safeguards to ensure a sufficient level data protection. Your personal data will only be transferred if the recipient is certified under the US-EU Privacy Shield Framework or if a standard contractual clause issued by the EU Commission has been concluded.
In certain circumstances and according to legislation it may be necessary to disclose data to public authorities. We may also disclose your personal data in order to establish exercise or defend our legal rights.
In the event of reorganisation or total or partial sale of the business, disclosure, if any, will in such connection take place in accordance with the legislation governing such processing of personal data at the time in question.
Updates to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy based on substantial changes in the legislation, new technical solutions, new or improved functions and to improve the website. If we make any substantial changes to the way we use your personal data we will notify you by email and by a prominent notification on our website.
Contact information
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed:
InterForm A/SSauntesvej 13DK 2820 Gentofte+45 36 99 26 84 Contact us here
About InterForm A/S
InterForm A/S has more than 30 years of experience developing solutions that improve the look and utility of business documents while reducing transaction costs.
Read more
InterForm products are marketed under the name ArtForm400 or ArtFormNG in North America.
Copyright © 2020 InterForm A/S.
This website uses Cookies to enhance your experience.
Thank you for your interest in InterXML400!
Please fill out the form below and we will contact you shortly with further information.
Form not found or is not publishedPowered by ChronoForms - ChronoEngine.com
You can also read more about the module on this page.- This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Best regards,
InterForm A/S
×
